[Music]
hello there it's been a while I've been
away my husband and I have been settling
in with our new family member a little a
fairy child that has brought us so much
love into our lives that we already
cannot imagine it any
[Music]
different I remember people warning me
that it was no easy feat to raise a
child in the same way that they warned
me it's not easy to change one's life to
start a new career to try something new
but experiences have led me to suspect
that many hard things are the most worth
doing time and again I found myself at
moments in my life where instead of
turning away from my fears I finally
face them and I'm often surprised to
find that they held the answers I was
searching for over time I started to
change my perspective the things that
challenge us can benefit us the most
just not in the way we may prefer
instead in the way we need no doubt the
experience of raising a baby has been
exhausting at times with long sleepless
nights many hours spent rocking singing
songs and taking in the fact that
everything is different now despite the
challenges it has been rewarding and
transformative
[Music]
I've been spending my time in a new kind
of slowness one that is shared with a
little human that only knows how to live
in the
present I have no doubt I will be
learning just as much from this baby as
they will be learning from me right now
there's no way to exist worrying about
the future or ruminating over the past
all that matters is now and suddenly I
realized that that's all I ever really
had
[Music]
I think when we accept more into our
lives we become aware of what there
isn't room for anymore consequently I've
been doing some internal decluttering
maybe you are too either way giving love
in some shape or form seems to
help I thought I would read out a little
poem I scribbl down this week while
soaking in the beauty of my garden in
bloom I hope you enjoy
it just maybe not all Mysteries are
meant to be unraveled some fears cannot
be resolved and explained try taking
them into the wild and offer it to all
that grows taste the heady scent of
flowers on your tongue and exclaim yes I
can place you here among beauty that is
too vast for me to fully
comprehend I am content for I've lived
in the fields long enough to know that
some things need to be understood not
with knowledge but by
knowing the relief of letting things be
as they once were a testament to all
that is wondrous and vast
it has been tricky to figure out how to
create videos while being a parent and I
have been navigating that it is um a
little challenging to find ways to film
but also have baby nearby while also
respecting his privacy as well he's
actually asleep over here
and uh he's being very quiet right now
which is not always the case a
interesting challenge that I have been
enjoying it has forced me to slow down a
lot more and I know this channel is a
lot about slowing down but this is
slowing down on a very physical level
physically doing so has been a really
interesting challenge for me and in a
really good way a very mindful
experience every step I take when
holding my baby I need to be careful
with I need to go downstairs very gently
and carefully I need to gracefully pour
myself some water because I don't want
to bump my baby's head with my arm or I
don't want to trip and fall and it's a a
very interesting pace and I I've really
enjoyed it I think I resisted it for a
little bit at first with every day I'm a
parent I realize your attitude and your
perspective regarding the lifestyle
changes you need to make um is all the
difference but yes since I've been
enjoying the flowers and all this
Abundant Life that has been growing this
late spring I'm so happy I've been able
to get so much footage of the late
Springtime and all that before I had my
baby and combining it with current um
Clips I've been spending a lot of time
at home walking the property nearby you
know walking the forest nearby I find
especially these days since I've been
obviously a little bit more tired
getting a little bit less sleep than
usual um I've been enjoying it even more
noticing even more and I suppose that's
what this channel is all about so I have
been up for the challenge for sure I of
course do have my Etsy shop open again I
am taking a very limited amount of
orders because I um am not capable of
doing what I used to do um my
productivity is my mother who is
infinitely wise keeps reminding me that
I am doing an incredibly productive and
important job I'm just balancing it with
more traditional work and um it has been
uh a really good thing to navigate make
sure I'm keeping a good life balance I
of course have videos and content on my
patreon as well as I have some things
available on my Etsy shop and the
hardback version of my book has been out
this year and I'm really happy with how
it turned out I think it came out um
looking really lovely better than I
expected so I was really happy about
that and um the paperback version as
well and so if you are ever interested
in supporting this channel those are
some ways you can but your well wishes
and your kindness and you just being
here is more than enough sending you all
so so much love goodbye
[Music]
all